Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1955; UP056.001.049.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1955; UP056.001.049.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
    American Institute of Chemical engineers; Alpha Kappa Delta. Alpha Tau Omega restrictive clause limits fraternity membership to white Christian males.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1955; UP056.001.049.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Paiting of murals by artists Matthew W. Boyhan and Nathaniel J. Jacobson [includes photo]; Academic Honors; pp. 1,8. [Administration] Bi-weekly payment plan explained. p. 1. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955-11-10; UP056.001.049.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Donald G. Abbott (1944). Joanna Camerlengo, New Publications Director (Includes photo). (page 6) Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1955-11-18; UP056.001.049.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1955; UP056.001.049.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 49)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of. Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1955; UP056.001.049.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1955; UP056.001.049.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1956; UP056.001.049.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1956; UP056.001.049.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1956; UP056.001.049.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1956; UP056.001.049.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 49)
    John Ahern. Appointed Sports Publicity Director. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1956; UP056.001.049.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1956; UP056.001.049.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1956; UP056.001.049.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1956; UP056.001.049.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 30, 1956; UP056.001.049.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 13, 1956; UP056.001.049.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1956; UP056.001.049.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1956; UP056.001.049.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1956; UP056.001.049.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1956; UP056.001.049.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 2, 1956; UP056.001.049.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1956; UP056.001.049.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1956; UP056.001.049.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 49)
    [Administration] Committee on Academic Standing establishes probation criteria. p. 5. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1956; UP056.001.049.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
    [Alpha Sigma Phi] Administration objects to house painted black {includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1956; UP056.001.049.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1956; UP056.001.049.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 14, 1956; UP056.001.050.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 21, 1956; UP056.001.050.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1956; UP056.001.050.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of; [Alpha Xi Delta] Jackson sorority withdrew from national group because of discriminatory policies, to continue locally
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1956; UP056.001.050.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1956; UP056.001.050.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1956; UP056.001.050.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1956; UP056.001.050.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [The Aesthetes] Organized October 16, 1956, p. 8.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1956; UP056.001.050.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Academic Honors; p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1956; UP056.001.050.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1956; UP056.001.050.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1956; UP056.001.050.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1956; UP056.001.050.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [Administration] (Buckley, James) Traffic Commission analyzes traffic problems; plans campus safety drive. p. 5.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1956; UP056.001.050.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [Administration] (Buckley, James) Traffic Commission analyzes traffic problems; plans campus safety drive. (photos) p. 1. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly ALpha Xi Delta). Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1957; UP056.001.050.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 8, 1957; UP056.001.050.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1957; UP056.001.050.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
    [alumni association] Martin L. Albert, Secretary Nickless tells what Tufts does to hold interest in the college
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1957; UP056.001.050.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1957; UP056.001.050.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1957; UP056.001.050.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1957; UP056.001.050.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1957; UP056.001.050.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 50)
    Alpha Kappa Delta; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1957; UP056.001.050.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1957; UP056.001.050.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1957; UP056.001.050.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1957; UP056.001.050.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1957; UP056.001.050.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1957; UP056.001.050.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1957; UP056.001.050.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 50)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 13, 1957; UP056.001.051.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 27, 1957; UP056.001.051.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Isabel Abbott, Appointed Director of Admissions (substituting for Mrs. Lovejoy on sick leave), p. 6.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1957; UP056.001.051.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1957; UP056.001.051.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1957; UP056.001.051.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1957; UP056.001.051.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Academic Honors; p.6. [Alpha Sigma Phi] Eight brothers donate blood at Tufts Surgical Center of Boston City Hospital [Includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1957; UP056.001.051.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1957; UP056.001.051.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 51)
    American institute of electrical engineering; Paul Abrahamian. Feature articles and photos of.; Academic Honors; pp. 1,5. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly ALpha Xi Delta).
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1957; UP056.001.051.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1957; UP056.001.051.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1957; UP056.001.051.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta).
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1957; UP056.001.051.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [Robert Alukonis, A1958] Paul Perito, preparing for a career in profesional or educational field
  - Tufts Weekly, December 20, 1957; UP056.001.051.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1958; UP056.001.051.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 23, 1958; UP056.001.051.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 3, 1958; UP056.001.051.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 7, 1958; UP056.001.051.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1958; UP056.001.051.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta to be reactivated
  - Tufts Weekly, February 19, 1958; UP056.001.051.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1958; UP056.001.051.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1958; UP056.001.051.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. p. 5. All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta to be reactivated
  - Tufts Weekly, March 5, 1958; UP056.001.051.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Student council opposed to reinstatement
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1958; UP056.001.051.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 12, 1958; UP056.001.051.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1958; UP056.001.051.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 19, 1958; UP056.001.051.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1958; UP056.001.051.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 26, 1958; UP056.001.051.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1958; UP056.001.051.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 2 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 9, 1958; UP056.001.051.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1958; UP056.001.051.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1958; UP056.001.051.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1958; UP056.001.051.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 23, 1958; UP056.001.051.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1958; UP056.001.051.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1958; UP056.001.051.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 30, 1958; UP056.001.051.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 2, 1958; UP056.001.051.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Alpha Tau Omega. [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 7, 1958; UP056.001.051.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1958; UP056.001.051.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 14, 1958; UP056.001.051.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1958; UP056.001.051.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1958; UP056.001.051.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 51)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 7, 1958; UP056.001.051.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 8, 1958; UP056.001.051.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 51)
    Academic Ceremonies 1958-59. Photo of academic procession.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 9, 1958; UP056.001.051.00046 (Volume Shared 134)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 12, 1958; UP056.001.052.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 17, 1958; UP056.001.052.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Alumni council] Twenty-fifth anniversary
  - Tufts Weekly, September 19, 1958; UP056.001.052.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 24, 1958; UP056.001.052.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 26, 1958; UP056.001.052.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Administration] Plus-minus marks. To be put into effect Fall, 1958. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1958; UP056.001.052.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-03; UP056.001.052.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Daniel C. Abbott (faculty). Director of orchestra and teacher of chorus. (page 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-08; UP056.001.052.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-10; UP056.001.052.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-15; UP056.001.052.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-17; UP056.001.052.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-22; UP056.001.052.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [American association of teachers of french] Tufts host Boston chapter
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-24; UP056.001.052.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1958-10-29; UP056.001.052.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1958; UP056.001.052.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1958; UP056.001.052.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1958; UP056.001.052.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1958; UP056.001.052.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1958; UP056.001.052.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1958; UP056.001.052.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1958; UP056.001.052.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 25, 1958; UP056.001.052.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1958; UP056.001.052.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1958; UP056.001.052.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 10, 1958; UP056.001.052.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1958; UP056.001.052.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 18, 1958; UP056.001.052.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1959; UP056.001.052.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1959; UP056.001.052.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1959; UP056.001.052.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 1 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 4, 1959; UP056.001.052.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 6, 1959; UP056.001.052.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1959; UP056.001.052.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Poet Wilbur Reads at Cohen Monday
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1959; UP056.001.052.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1959; UP056.001.052.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Dr. Crook named Psychology Head
  - Tufts Weekly, February 20, 1959; UP056.001.052.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 1. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1959; UP056.001.052.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1959; UP056.001.052.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Convalescing from illness, p. 5.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1959; UP056.001.052.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    U Thittila, Buddhist Monk, VIists Tufts Community for Five Days; Class Appearances Highlight Stay
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1959; UP056.001.052.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Debating Society places second in Hofstra meet
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1959; UP056.001.052.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [President Herbert] Hoover Recieves Ballou Medal
    Hoover, Herbert C.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1959; UP056.001.052.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Interdorm Award at Jackson
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1959; UP056.001.052.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Council Hears Negative Mayorality Sentiment; [American association of teacher of french] French speaking contest
  - Tufts Weekly, March 26, 1959; UP056.001.052.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    [Alethea Sorority] New Jackson local social group formed (formerly Alpha Xi Delta). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 8, 1959; UP056.001.052.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Oxford Chemist Gives Science and Religion Lecture on Friday
  - Tufts Weekly, April 10, 1959; UP056.001.052.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Christie Allan (J 1962) Performs in "Ice Chips" presented by Skating Club of Boston.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 15, 1959; UP056.001.052.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Alpha Sigma Phi. Freeland K. Abbott, (faculty) 1959, Recipient of U.S. Educational grant under auspices of Fulbright Act to conduct research in contemporary Islam at University of Karachi in Pakistan, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1959; UP056.001.052.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1959; UP056.001.052.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1959; UP056.001.052.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Space Exposition Opens here Friday
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1959; UP056.001.052.00051 (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1959; UP056.001.052.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1959; UP056.001.052.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Dr. Rethis Lectures at Tufts tomorrow night; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1959; UP056.001.052.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Prof. Frederick Weaver Retires after 40 years
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1959; UP056.001.052.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Fletcher School Celebrates 25th Anniversary. Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 6, 1959; UP056.001.052.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 52)
    Alumni day; [Allen, George V.] Speaker at Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Commencement banquet, 1959.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 19, 1959; UP056.001.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 25, 1959; UP056.001.053.00002 (Box 53)
    [Administration] Changes in [administration]. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 2, 1959; UP056.001.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 9, 1959; UP056.001.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 16, 1959; UP056.001.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1959; UP056.001.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1959; UP056.001.053.00007 (Box 53)
    Freeland K. Abbott, In Pakistan doing research on "Social and Cultural Changes in Islam and Pakistan," p. 9.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1959; UP056.001.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 13, 1959; UP056.001.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 20, 1959; UP056.001.053.00010 (Box 53)
    [Admissions] Administered under John C. Palmer. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1959; UP056.001.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 11, 1959; UP056.001.053.00012 (Box 53)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [alumni council] Committee formed to standardize college colors; [American association of University Professors] Tufts chapter chides mandatory oaths for federal loans
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1959; UP056.001.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 8, 1960; UP056.001.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 15, 1960; UP056.001.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 21, 1960; UP056.001.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 12, 1960; UP056.001.053.00017 (Box 53)
    [Allen, Catherine L.] Coordinator of Special Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 19, 1960; UP056.001.053.00018 (Box 53)
    [alumni council] Committee formed to standardize college colors; [Administration] Faculty group appointed by Administrative Registration Study Committee studies registration. p. 5. [Administration] Faculty group appointed by Administrative Registration Study Committee studies registration.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 26, 1960; UP056.001.053.00019 (Box 53)
    [Alumni council] New policy offers courses to alumni, faculty, staff members and friends
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1960; UP056.001.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1960; UP056.001.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1960; UP056.001.053.00022 (Box 53)
    Academy of American Poets; Poetry contest open to Tufts students; P.6.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1960; UP056.001.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1960; UP056.001.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1960; UP056.001.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 15, 1960; UP056.001.053.00026 (Box 53)
    Alethea Sorority. [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 22, 1960; UP056.001.053.00027 (Box 53)
    [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1960; UP056.001.053.00028 (Box 53)
    [All Around Club] Father-Daughter Weekend. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1960; UP056.001.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1960; UP056.001.053.00030 (Box 53)
    Alpha Sigma Phi; [American association of teacher of spanish and portuguese] Tufts host to Boston Spanish contest of the Pan American society of New England
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1960; UP056.001.053.00031 (Box 53)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Action to reactivate
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1960; UP056.001.053.00032 (Box 53)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi; [Alpha Xi Delta] action to reactivate not approved; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, September 16, 1960; UP056.001.054.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 54)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 23, 1960; UP056.001.054.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 54)